O Sun-blessed and free nation, bring happiness and salvation to your people.
You are my friend's companion and merciful!
Let your fame shine as long as the world exists!
This golden canyon, my dear Uzbekistan
You have the souls of your brave ancestors!
A time when the power of great people rises up
A country that captivated the world!
The generous Uzbek faith that will never disappear
The free and young generation are your powerful wings!
Lights of independence, guardians of peace
Truth-loving motherland, prosper forever!
This golden gorge, beloved Uzbekistan
You have the souls of your brave ancestors!
A time when the power of great people rises up
A country that captivated the world!